Subtitles are color-coded by country,
and this setting cannot be changed.
No, no, find the spot that works for you.
-Take your time.
-Yeah, you're good.
-Go, Amotti, come on!
-Take your time.
This is our chance, man.
Eddie, Amotti's gassing.
This is already…
-This is already at that.
-He's gassing.
Yeah.
-Don't let it shake you.
-Keep your nerve!
-Let's go!
-You got this.
Amotti, you can
swing it twice before throwing.
Use your hips. Up!
Breathe, Amotti.
-Up!
-Up, up!
It went over!
Good work, mate.
-Good throw, Amotti.
-Good job, Amotti.
-You okay?
-Are you all right?
You're okay.
It's all good. I got this.
I kept pushing myself into the zone.
I told myself to stay focused.
This is our chance, bro.
We felt like we definitely had a good shot
at taking out Korea in this last event.
-Come on!
-Take your time!
You've totally got this.
Just keep breathing.
Hip thrust!
-Yeah!
-Nice!
-Let's go, Justo!
-Let's go!
Let's go!
Easy!
Let's go, Justo!
-All right!
-Let's go!
Come on! Swing twice!
-That's it, that's it.
-There you go! You got this!
You were born for this.
Baba Booey!
Let's go, Justo.
-Piece of cake!
-Justo!
It's all you!
The Philippines, the hope and morale,
sky high.
Justin's doing good.
-Mate's consistent.
-He's doing very good.
-He's good.
-Yeah, I know.
The guy's strong.
You've got this!
You all day, Justin.
It felt like we made the right choice.
Because I know he can do it properly,
and I think, at least,
he can get second place.
All right! Oh damn.
Get it, Amotti. Come on.
You're at the finish line.
I'm counting on you.
Just keep at it a little longer!
You got this, Justin. You got this!
Hip drive!
The game's almost over!
I think he needs to get closer.
We'll be fine.
I saw Amotti committing mistakes.
It got my hopes up.
I tried to throw it faster.
-Hip extension!
-Up!
So Amotti wouldn't be able to rest long.
Come on!
-Let's go!
-Come on!
-Let's go, Justin!
-Come on, Justin!
The Filipinos are riding high right now,
and their cheering is really fired up.
It's okay, take your time.
That's what confidence does.
But on our side,
things felt weirdly subdued,
so I tried to turn the mood around.
You've totally got this. Easy!
You're too close.
-You're too close.
-Too close?
I was rattled.
It threw me off every time
and I couldn't understand
why it wouldn't go over.
Hang in there, Justin.
You're almost there.
It's going to be over any time now.
This is it! It's over!
-It's over!
Let's go, Justin!
-Come on, Amotti, go!
-Last one!
Ten seconds! Come on, Amotti. Full power!
-This is really it now!
-Let's go, Justin!
It's all right.
-There's still time.
-Keep your head!
I kept praying,
"Come on, Amotti."
-Keep your head!
-Yes!
Nice!
-Good work, mate.
-Good throw, Amotti.
This is too nerve-racking to watch.
Man.
I didn't know when to add power
and when to let go of the ball.
It wasn't a movement
that was familiar to me,
which is why I kept botching it.
Getting the hang of it took some time.
He's gassing though.
-Amotti's struggling.
-Yeah!
He's wasting energy.
-Okay!
-All right!
-Yeah, nicely done, mate.
-Good one!
We're in big trouble now.
We're in big, big trouble.
It's a good day for an upset, team.
It's a good day for an upset.
The weight of the sack
-will now be increased.
-Heavier? Heavier.
That's crazy.
That already looks heavy as f***.
Right. The third one is really heavy now.
This is nothing to you.
Just keep doing what you're doing, Justin!
I know that whenever
they increase the weight,
it's favorable for me,
because I saw Amotti
committing mistakes with a lighter weight.
So now that it's heavier,
I know that there's more chance of him
committing more mistakes.
So I thought this was my chance already.
If I failed here, everything
we'd done so far would be wasted.
I needed to push myself harder.
-Focus on getting it right the first time.
-Okay.
-You're doing great.
-I know it's tough.
Stand by.
Let's go, Eddie! Get the rig out. Come on!
-Go, Eddie.
-That's the Australian way, brother!
-Get the rig out!
-Ready…
All right, let's do this!
-Looking good.
-Bring it.
Give it your best shot, Amotti!
You got this, Justin!
Make your countries proud!
Yes, Eddie. Nice.
It's getting higher!
Yeah, it's going further.
The ball's getting heavier,
and it's going further.
It flew through the air so easily,
like he was tossing a bag of trash.
That's definitely heavier.
Heavier.
-Go, Justo.
-You got this, Justin!
More power! Crank it up!
For my body weight and for my strength,
I found the sack manageable.
Justo, feeling good, bro.
You're a triathlete.
Let's go!
Go, Amotti!
Come on, focus and get it over in one go.
It was definitely heavier.
I needed to focus
and get it over in my first attempt.
-Yes!
-Nice!
-Nicely done, Amotti!
-Good job.
-Yes!
-All right!
-Nice!
-You can stand a bit closer.
-Okay.
Easy money, Eddie.
He doesn't even need a windup.
Just straight into it.
Yeah, that's the best.
He backs up and he goes…
There's no reset.
Yes, Eddie!
Breathe. Focus.
Go, Justin!
Give it more power.
Yeah, nice!
Beautiful, Justin!
All right, Amotti. Just focus on yourself.
Don't worry about anyone else.
-That's it!
-Nice!
Nice, Amotti. Nice!
There's the scream!
This is hard to watch.
My heart can't take it.
He's waning, Justo.
Amotti must be tired already.
He's having a hard time.
I actually got excited.
But even then,
I'm really going to give my best.
You got this, Justin!
Let's go, Justin!
-Easy.
-Yes!
Let's go, Amotti.
-Amotti, that spot was perfect.
-Perfect spot just now.
-The perfect spot to release the ball.
-Yeah.
Let's go, Eddie.
Let's go, Eddie. Let's go!
-Nice!
Nice, Justin.
Make it count, Amotti. Let's go.
One… Get it in one go.
-Yes!
-Nice!
-He's back!
-Beautiful!
That's why he's a champion.
That's why he's a champion,
because once he's found his rhythm,
he doesn't miss.
Spot on. Keep doing this!
-Easy!
-That's it!
I finally got the hang of it.
I felt like I wouldn't miss another throw.
-He's got the hang of it.
-He's on fire.
I think he's got it down now.
Yeah, he's totally dialed in now.
-He knows the feeling of it now. Yeah.
-He knows he needs to get it in one.
Nice. Set and up.
That's my guy!
It's getting higher!
Poor Justin's gotta run to it
and run back.
Yeah.
And he keeps having to grab that.
He basically only gets
25 seconds to throw it.
You got this.
-Go again, Justo.
-Yeah.
He missed? Yes, that's it.
-Here we go.
-This is it!
Let's do this.
Reset!
You can do this. Have faith!
-Just reset.
-Hip extension. Go!
-Yeah, bro!
-Yes!
All right! Let's do this!
-Focus, Amotti! You got this!
-It's neck and neck!
That's it.
One, two… In one go!
-Beautiful!
-Yes!
Nice, Amotti!
Great throw. Good job.
I saw that Amotti is getting better
at throwing the ball,
not committing mistakes anymore.
It made me feel like I'm in trouble.
Throw it out far.
Closer, Eddie.
-He's saying that because he's struggling.
-What did he say?
He told him not to throw it far.
It was nothing against the Philippines.
I was just throwing it.
My technique to kind of keep me in rhythm,
because I can conserve more energy.
He's struggling.
Team Philippines is struggling.
He's gassed out.
Look how much he's sweating.
Legs!
He can't afford to rest.
-Really?
-Trick shot!
Nice break!
-Use the rest.
-Yeah.
-Justo, use the rest.
-Justo, recover.
We had to pause
while they retrieved the ball,
which gave Hernandez a break.
Come on, let's get going.
We've got to keep going while he's tired.
Stand by.
Go, Justo. Nice recovery.
-Let's go, bro!
-Full swing.
Ready…
-Get ready.
-Come on, Justin.
-Go.
-Go, go. Eighteen, seventeen seconds.
Deep breath.
-Come on, fire it up.
-Let's go, bro!
Yes!
Nice.
Come on, Justo.
He's cutting it close.
Get it in one go.
Focus.
-All right!
-Nice! Great throw!
The time limit
will now be reduced to 20 seconds.
All right, here we go.
Now it's crunch time, Eddie.
Try speeding up at the beginning,
just in case.
-Focus and get it in one.
-You'll be fine.
You've got no time to f****** mess around.
Let's go, Justin. You got this.
Just keep doing what you're doing.
He doesn't look at all fazed.
I'm so hungry.
We're gonna make up for that.
-We're gonna feast tonight.
-We're gonna make up for that tonight.
We're gonna feast. We deserve it.
100%.
Let's go, Eddie.
Twenty seconds, bro.
Make sure!
-Nice!
-Yeah, bro!
-All right!
-Yes!
-Good shit, Amotti.
-Nice, Amotti.
You guys are killing it.
It's a tight match.
-Everyone's just like, "Wow!"
-Yeah.
Eddie's downplaying how hard
-this challenge is.
-Oh yeah.
For the country!
-Nice!
-Nice one.
Swing!
-Yeah!
-Nice!
That was a good throw, Justin.
He's good. He's really good.
He's nailed when to let go.
The team and South Korea's fate
is in your hands.
-Yes!
-There you go.
Beautiful!
-Yes!
-Nice! Too easy.
-Amotti's f****** very good.
-Yeah.
Amotti's an animal, dude.
Yeah, such an animal.
He's found his rhythm,
and he's just hitting it.
-He's not even sweating.
-No.
Amotti's not getting tired.
-He's strong.
-Yeah, he's a beast.
Jeez, how many times is this?
At least a hundred.
-Nice!
-Yeah, bro!
All day, Justin.
Go, Amotti!
Why is he so good though?
I can't believe they're still going.
I wonder how long
they've been going for now.
A long time.
-Yes!
-Nice!
The time limit
will now be reduced to 15 seconds.
Fifteen?
Justo, you don't get a chance
to make a mistake anymore.
Yeah, first time every time, bro.
Work on that power.
I just know that you cannot commit
any mistakes anymore,
so it's a game of
whoever commits the first mistake.
Whoever commits a mistake will lose.
You really have to get it in one go now.
-It's about focus.
-Yeah, it's about focus now.
A game of who messes up.
One mistake, and it's over.
I've got to get it over in one go
without a single misstep.
Time to run over these guys, Ed.
He's hungry to win, he's hungry to eat.
Time to eat, Eddie.
Time to eat, baby.
-Let's go eat.
I'm confident in Eddie not being beaten.
He's gonna absolutely demolish this quest.
Stand by.
-Let's go, Eddie.
-Here we go!
It's what you were built for, Justin.
You were built for this!
Ready…
-This is it. This is where it ends.
-Let's go!
Easy, Ed.
Power swing, Justin!
Come on, Justin. Get under.
From the first one, man.
Don't take two throws, just one.
Get it in one.
If he misses this, that's it.
Nice!
-That was a close shave.
-Let's go!
-Come on!
-Yes, get it in one go.
Get it in one. Don't rush. Nice big dip.
-All right!
-That's it!
Let's go.
Yes, Eddie.
All day, all night.
-Let's go, Justin. Dig deep.
-Dig deeper.
This is the one, bro. This is it!
-For the country!
-Justin, this is all you all day!
-Yes!
-Nice!
Come on, Justin!
We're almost there, Amotti.
He was cutting it close,
but he was getting them over.
So I told myself to assume
I was going to be up
and to just concentrate on my own throws.
-Yes!
-Nice!
Get her up.
-Good position, bro. There it is.
-Nice.
One big swing.
Hold your breath. Big squat.
-Nice.
-Nice!
Focus and throw up in one go.
-That's it!
-Nice!
No one's missing,
and it's putting pressure on him
because the turnaround's so quick.
-Keep strong.
-Deep swing.
Big, deep swing.
One mistake. That's all it takes.
Yup!
-Go! Go, go!
-One more. Five seconds.
One mistake, and it's over.
-Five seconds.
-Pick it up, pick it up.
-You got this.
-Come on!
-Let's go!
-Come on, Justin!
Unbelievable.
He did that with a second to go.
-Focus, Amotti!
-Focus!
Almost there! That's your motivation!
Yes, that's it!
It's yours to take now, Jae-hong.
This is it!
Yeah, nice.
Let's go. Use that time.
You're a little bit off.
Come on, miss just this once.
Just this once.
-Deep swing!
Full extension!
-Nice!
-Nice, brother!
-Nice, brother! Good job!
All right.
Focus now.
In one go!
-All right.
-Oh no.
-Come on, focus. Throw it right up.
-Focus, focus.
I was thinking in my head,
"Please commit another mistake
so that this ends already,
and so I don't get tired anymore."
-All right!
-Nice!
Focus your energy on
getting it right the first time.
Recover. Breathe.
Dial it, Justin. Come on, focus, brother.
Justin, this is you all day. Keep going.
You're doing amazing. Keep it up.
Big swing!
-Go, go!
-Come on!
We're good. This is it.
Come on, miss. Please don't get it over.
-Go, go!
-Come on!
Justin, this is you. Come on!
Down… Up!
It was like
a life-and-death situation for me.
Game over.
I did it.
I can't believe it.
Even I was filled with doubt,
thinking I wasn't going to make it.
But I did make it.
I'm happy.
I'm thrilled.
Man, that was insane!
When it was over,
I was so happy that I almost cried.
The guy's a hero. He deserves a medal.
This is unbelievable. How good was he?
You can breathe now, Seung-yeon.
I know that was rough on you.
I'd been feeling really guilty.
I was really anxious early on in the game.
I honestly thought we'd lost.
I was like, "We've lost,
and it's all because of me."
Seung-yeon, that was well fought!
I'm not even religious,
but I was praying
to every god in existence.
I felt like I was standing on
the edge of a cliff about to jump off,
when Amotti came
and grabbed me by my hand.
I'm just thrilled.
I owe him big time.
He always comes through.
Very good game.
-Nice game, nice game.
-It's okay, it's okay. It's okay, guys.
-Hey. No.
-Sorry, guys. I did my best.
No, dude, you did…
-Nice game.
-Dude. You did great, brother.
You did awesome.
I actually don't have any regrets
because I know that I did my best.
But what I couldn't handle,
and what was really hard for me to handle,
was letting down my team.
Justin really showed
how much of a beast he actually is,
and again, epitomizing
what that Filipino fighting spirit is.
I have a great sense of respect and pride,
not only for Justin, but for
all the athletes in Team Philippines.
The Philippines, in third place,
has been eliminated from the competition.
GROUP A FINAL RESULTS
Raise those heads high, guys.
You gave it everything.
It was so close though.
Team Philippines has been eliminated
from Physical: Asia.
Each team member
will now destroy their torso.
I hope that I and we
made the country proud
with all our efforts.
We gave it everything we had,
and we were determined
to show Filipino fighting spirit.
We didn't have anyone in our team
that just gave up.
We really gave it our all…
and will into the events.
It was extremely proud for me,
as the captain, to witness that.
Now, a lot feels unfinished.
We will only get stronger
from this experience.
We couldn't have made it this far
if we hadn't worked together as a team.
Let's fight!
-Philippines!
Jeepney blitz!
Every ounce of determination…
One, two, three, up!
To collaborate…
You're okay.
Amazing.
…to share.
That's Team Philippines,
and we've come this far…
as a team.
It was my dream to compete.
It was the best opportunity in my life.
It was an absolute honor
representing the Philippines.
I wasn't gonna cry.
As athletes and as individuals,
it's been amazing.
It's been a great opportunity
to be selected, to be among you guys.
I'm so sad that we're leaving.
Although I'm very sad that
this is gonna be our last challenge
and we've been eliminated,
I'm still very happy to be able to compete
and participate alongside
my awesome and wonderful teammates.
-He did really well.
-Yeah, he did.
Thank you, everyone.
-Proud of you guys, bro.
-Good luck, guys.
Appreciate it, man. Thank you so much.
The Philippines is strong.
-It was awesome competing with you.
-You too.
-Great job, great job.
-Thank you. Well done. Go hard.
One last time, one last time.
-Ready?
-This is it.
-This is the loudest. Okay, ready?
-This is the loudest.
Let's fight!
-Philippines!
PHYSICAL: ASIA
7. FOR THE HOMELAND
What's this?
Are we walking on clouds or something?
I know, right?
When we walked through the doors,
we saw sandy ground and random pillars.
We had no idea what was going on.
I think that's for hanging in the air.
This is my turf then.
This arena feels kind of different.
Are we meant to be hanging in midair?
I wondered
what sort of torture awaited us,
given how many crazy games there'd been.
The third quest of Physical: Asia.
Team rep match.
The games will now be revealed.
Sack toss match.
Toss it over those?
The last one hanging match.
It's a hanging contest.
The totem hold match.
That's a strength contest.
Zigzag hurdle match.
We're meant to just
keep jumping over them?
How do we jump over them?
Once all the games are finished,
the scores will be tallied.
In the event of a tie,
the final ranking will be determined
by the results of the first game,
the zigzag hurdle match.
Now, please select
your representatives for each game.
I'll be there forever.
Maybe I'll turn into a monkey.
Lkhagva-Ochir, just treat it like
one of your acrobatic stunts.
Pretend you're performing.
That's got Khandsuren written all over it.
She's a volleyball player,
so she can change direction mid-sprint.
I was thinking I could do it with Dulguun.
DULGUUN ENKHBAT
NATIONAL TEAM BASKETBALL PLAYER
You guys have an edge
because you can run dynamically.
Most people can only run
in a straight line
and don't have the agility
to twist and turn while running.
Look, Team Türkiye's picking
the female wrestler for the sack toss.
-The sack toss? You sure about that?
-That's me all over.
How many times do I have to throw it?
You just keep throwing it
until you can't anymore.
As many times as I can?
I think every team will send
their heaviest players to the totems.
Then I'll do the totems.
What else would I do?
I'm not good for anything else.
This is where strategy comes in.
We're not trying to place first
in all the games.
We just need one first place
and two second places.
Sure, winning everything would be perfect,
but it's not necessary.
That's the first game.
The first game
determines the overall ranking
-So that's the important one.
-in the event of a tie.
Shouldn't Kana and I take that one?
You mean I go first
and you do the final sprint?
What? You want to do the running one?
Don't you think we should do that one?
That's the important one.
It was something I was confident in,
and I was hell-bent
on taking down Team Türkiye.
I still hadn't forgotten that incident.
And since I'm a fast runner,
I put my hand up for that game.
The third quest of Physical: Asia.
Team rep match.
The two representatives from each country
participating in the zigzag hurdle match,
please make your way to the arena.
-Let's go.
-In the name of Allah.
Let's go!
Let's go, team!
We got this!
We got this.
I think we have the edge over the others.
Our two will be perfect for jumping.
Mongolia chose to go
with their tall players.
Maybe they think
it'll make jumping easier?
-Could it?
-I guess.
Then should we have gone
with someone taller too?
The pillar was hip-height
for both Dulguun and me.
So jumping over it
wasn't a problem for us.
As long as we didn't slip up,
we could score some points here.
I was very confident.
It's quite high.
We might not be able to
jump over it in one go.
It's quite high for Soichi.
Given that my legs are short,
I figured it might be hard for me
to jump the hurdle.
So I thought it'd be more effective for me
to focus on speed
in areas other than the jumps.
That girl looks light on her feet.
She was a track athlete, right?
Yeah.
Winning's the only thing on our minds.
We don't care who we're up against.
All I'm focusing on is jumping the hurdle
as quickly as possible.
The first game of the team rep match,
the zigzag hurdle match.
Once the whistle blows,
the match will begin.
Khandsuren, no need to rush.
Just go at your own pace.
Keep your head, don't stress.
-Let's go!
-You got this!
Stand by.
We want explosive speed.
It's just ten laps.
Ready…
Khandsuren, you're in the lead.
Love it, love it.
-Nice one!
-Nice!
-Hey, you've got to hit it!
-Hit the button!
There you go. That's it.
It's okay. Don't sweat it!
Don't forget to hit the bell.
Mongolia messed up.
Bravo!
-Nice, Ali!
-Bravo!
Sorry.
-Sorry.
-It's all right.
It was harder than I thought it would be,
and I was panicking
because I was lagging behind
Team Türkiye and Team Mongolia.
Even with ten laps, I thought
I'd be fine as long as I kept my pace,
as the others were bound
to get tired at some point.
I just had to keep at it.
Don't rush it! Keep your cool!
Come on, Khandsuren! Keep going!
It's okay. It's okay.
Yes, you've caught up!
You've caught up!
-Good pace!
-You're doing great!
She lost ground
after missing the bell at the start.
Keep your cool, Khandsuren!
You're doing great.
Breathe.
I panicked
after forgetting to hit the bell.
I went into a tailspin.
I was gasping for air,
forgetting to breathe,
and falling down.
But my teammates were watching,
and beating myself up
wasn't going to help.
That's great, Khandsuren.
Go, go.
So I tried my hardest to focus on
just getting through those ten laps.
Ali, everyone else is already struggling!
Ali, they're gassing out!
You've got a whole lap on them!
Keep pulling away!
The sooner you're done,
the sooner I can finish.
Come on, Ali!
Come on, keep pushing.
Last three!
Everyone's struggling!
That's it! Go, go!
Yes, that's it.
Hit it. Run!
-Come on!
-Final push, last two!
Only two to go!
Come on, Ali. Last one.
Last one!
Nefise, get ready!
Keep pushing till the end!
You got this!
Run! Last one!
Great pace!
That's a great pace!
Good stuff, Soichi!
Great pace! One.
It wasn't just high.
It was also wide,
so it took a decent amount
of effort to clear.
It was harder than it looked, for sure.
But one lap in,
and I knew I could catch them.
I told myself
there was no more room for error.
The Japanese guy's closing in.
Nefise, pick it up just a bit more!
Pick it up!
Don't slow down, Nefise! Keep pushing!
Japan's taken the lead.
Come on, pick it up!
To be honest,
it was way too high for me
to actually jump over.
And I just got so fixated on that,
wondering why I wasn't able to
clear it properly.
I was so confident going in
that I didn't see that coming at all.
-Come on.
-Go.
Yes, Dulguun, looking good!
Go, Dulguun! That's the way to do it!
Yes, Dulguun! Yes!
Even if we couldn't get first place,
we needed at least second
to advance to the next quest.
-Come on, almost done!
-Pick it up, Nefise!
Come on! Faster!
Come on, Dulguun! You're doing great!
Keep pushing, Nefise!
Türkiye's down and out!
Yes, Dulguun.
We've got to hold onto second place.
Just two more.
He closed the gap! We're neck and neck!
We've caught up to Türkiye!
Go, go! Come on!
Last one!
Keep that pace!
Come on!
You got this, Soichi!
Yes, Hashimoto!
-Nice, nice!
-Let's go!
I was absolutely certain I'd clinched this
as I went to claim the flag.
You can slow down! No need to rush!
Yeah!
-Go, Nefise!
-You've got to pick it up!
You're almost there. Keep pushing!
Last one!
You can catch her in this last one!
Go, go!
I think we've got it.
My heart rate was through the roof.
I was completely wrecked.
You're almost done! Come on!
Run, Nefise!
I was sure I could catch up to her.
-You're reeling in Türkiye!
-Yes!
Yes!
Come on, run!
Come on! Mongolia's closing in!
Book it! Straight on!
Come on!
He's gassed out!
I was going so well
when I just wiped out from exhaustion
out of nowhere.
Team Türkiye literally won by a hair.
I was crushed.
Game over.
-Yes! Beautifully done!
-Great job, Nefise!
Bravo!
It's my fault.
Regret hit me hard.
I didn't bring my A-game,
and I didn't live up
to my team's expectations.
All of this just hit me,
and I started crying.
It's because I fell.
Don't worry about it.
I really hoped to win at least two points.
When I heard the score,
I was super bummed.
We have to come first
in the second game, no matter what.
The next one's
a one-on-one against Türkiye.
Mongolia's out.
They're locked in last place.
We win this one,
take the game, and get three points.
He caught up to your lead.
Crank it up this time, okay?
All right.
The Turkish girl's pretty wrecked, right?
Yeah, she was slow.
You did well. Come on.
-I should've gone first.
-Okay, let's try that.
Japan is next level, man.
Hashimoto crushed that.
Yeah, Japanese athletes have technique,
and they train hard.
I was fast, right?
You were fast as hell.
Your legs might not lift
as much as you think,
-so try and exaggerate the movement.
-Okay.
You've worked up your body now,
so this round won't feel as tough.
Your breathing should be fine too.
The second round of the first game,
the zigzag hurdle match.
Stand by.
This is the final round, so go all out.
-Go, Japan!
-You got this!
Go, Japan!
I'm feeling good about this.
The track girl's already spent.
I'm wiped,
but I've got to show them how tough I am.
I'm sure we're going to win this.
Find your rhythm, okay?
Ready…
Pull ahead.
Come on, Nefise!
Let's do this!
Shrink the gap, and I'll overtake them.
Keep going.
Shrink that gap.
Push. Don't let the gap widen.
Push. Don't walk.
Stay on pace, keep the tempo!
She's flagging. Türkiye's behind by a lap.
She's behind by a lap!
-Japan is just so much better.
-Yeah.
Look at her hand technique.
See how she pushes?
She has great technique. Just look at her.
-Nefise! Nefise!
Hang in there!
The second round was sheer agony.
I was on the verge of passing out,
but I forced myself to keep going.
Japan's struggling too, Nefise!
She can't jump either!
She's also struggling!
That's okay. You're doing fine.
Get that leg up!
Awesome!
Don't rush. Keep it steady!
You're ahead by two laps!
Last one.
Go!
-Nice!
-Last one!
Last one!
Ali can win this. Close the gap for him!
Just take some pressure off him!
Don't give up, Nefise!
Come on, Soichi!
-That's it, come on!
-Let's go!
Yes, Soichi!
You can do this, Nefise!
Go, Ali, go!
-Ali's good, isn't he?
-Yeah.
He's got good lower-body strength.
Japan can slip up at any point.
I just have to wait for it to happen.
And while waiting for him to slip up,
I did my best to close the gap
as fast as I could.
It's not over till the flag's taken,
so I just kept going.
-Go, Soichi!
-Final stretch!
We did it!
I was stoked.
I'd been wanting to settle the score
with Team Türkiye so badly,
and I did so by a landslide.
It felt great.
A loss in the first game
would've been disastrous for the team,
so I was thrilled and relieved to win.
Great job.
Sorry, Ali.
Don't worry about it.
Seriously, I was so close to throwing up.
-I'm sorry.
-Look, it's okay. Get up.
We did well.
-Good job.
-Good job, guys.
We got two points. We're good.
I was really sad.
I remained on edge
even after the game was over.
It was totally my fault.
I admit it, I could've done better.
I just handed the win to Team Japan
on a silver platter.
I'm telling you though,
their winning streak ends here.
Physical: Asia.
The two representatives from each country
participating in the totem hold match,
please make your way to the arena.
In the name of Allah. Let's go!
-Let's go!
You got this. You've totally got this.
YUSHIN OKAMI
MMA FIGHTER
KATSUMI NAKAMURA
NATIONAL TEAM SWIMMER
Come on, boys!
This second game demands
both muscle endurance and body weight,
so we strategically went with two guys.
You might think they have the edge
because they're two guys,
but this is anyone's game.
What I want from my teammates
is to have a bit more faith in our team
and to show them what Turks are made of,
just like we did in the opening quest.
We're just as good
in individual challenges.
Recep Kara and Yasemin Adar.
Yasemin's a crazy strong woman.
YASEMIN ADAR YIGIT
NATIONAL TEAM WRESTLER
I want to demonstrate
how strong women can be,
especially Turkish women.
I'm a very strong woman,
as strong as any man out there.
Recep will be taking on the hardest task.
They're both incredibly strong.
-You got this!
-Let's go!
Come on, Türkiye!
Let's go, team!
Crush them!
ENKH-ORGIL
MMA FIGHTER
ADIYASUREN
NATIONAL TEAM JUDOKA
Do you think this is
too tough for Adiyasuren?
It did kind of worry us.
I mean, anyone can see
Enkh-Orgil's a small guy.
Regardless, I still thought
that Enkh-Orgil and Adiyasuren
would be able to hold their own.
Being tall with long arms
means the totems will lean over more,
whereas if you're small,
it's easier for you to find your base.
I had faith in myself.
I do judo,
which involves a lot of gripping,
so I thought I had an advantage
in holding on to the totems.
But my heart was pounding so hard
that I could actually hear it.
I was a nervous wreck.
Because we lost two points
in the previous game,
it was crucial
to win them back in this game.
Let's push till the end for the team.
-You're the best!
-Looking good, Adiyasuren!
You got this.
Physical: Asia.
The totem hold match.
Once the whistle blows,
the match will begin.
When the whistle goes,
we pull together first and then ease up.
In the name of Allah.
Believe in yourselves. You can do this!
Let's go!
You got this!
Ready…
-All right, looking good!
-Looking great, guys!
Don't move around too much!
Stay tight and balanced. Stay in balance.
Way to go, guys! You're as still as rocks.
Don't jolt them
by pulling too hard, Recep.
Don't jolt them.
It wasn't too bad.
The weight didn't feel too heavy.
Take deep breaths and don't look around.
That's it. Keep breathing.
There you go, nice.
You're doing great, guys!
Perfect, you're like statues!
Everyone else is shifting around.
All we did was focus on the task at hand
right through to the end.
Unfortunately,
due to an issue with the safety pin…
Due to a mechanical fault,
our team had to redo the challenge.
DUE TO AN EQUIPMENT MALFUNCTION,
THE GAME PROCEEDED AND CONCLUDED
WITH THE SAFETY PIN
FOR TEAM JAPAN'S TOTEM PARTIALLY ENGAGED
AS PER THE RULES,
TEAMS MONGOLIA AND TÜRKIYE'S TIMES STAND
WHILE JAPAN WILL REDO THE GAME
IN 40 HOURS UNDER SAME CONDITIONS
TO DETERMINE GROUP B'S RANKINGS FOR GAME 2
This was decided after discussion,
and as sportsmen, we'll go along with it.
It was decided
that we'd redo the challenge
after the third and fourth games.
Look, the right side's about to go.
-Team Mongolia's going to fold soon.
-That grip on the right is loosening.
How's it going over there?
Fine. You?
You there?
I feel like I'm getting pulled.
-I'm getting pulled, but--
-Pulled?
-The weight isn't evenly distributed.
-Really?
I felt like
I was on the verge of letting go.
I was scared
that I wasn't going to be able to hold on.
I'm taking a lot of the weight right now.
I think they pull on me more
because I'm taller than you.
Yeah?
-Should I pull tighter?
-Wait.
Then I can't bear any weight.
-Let's balance the weight between us.
-Okay.
Stop pulling and jolting them.
Keep them as still as possible.
It was tough to stay in sync,
so we kept shifting.
We kept trying to split the weight
evenly between us.
We communicated, kept each other in check,
and made sure to adjust
until we managed to get
an even distribution.
They're doing well.
This feels great now.
Tell me if your hands get tired.
-Okay.
-Could you just…
Oh, that's perfect. That's it.
Team Türkiye's freaky.
They're going strong.
Look, they're not moving.
-They haven't shifted at all.
-They're totally fixed.
I think their strategy
is to move as little as possible.
Don't worry, guys. You're the most solid.
-You're amazing. You look so calm.
-You two look totally chill.
I thought we'd easily
take first place in this.
I kept telling myself
that I could be here all day
and that holding these totems
was a piece of cake to me.
Looking amazing, Recep.
-Don't turn your head.
-Great form.
Don't turn to the left, Yasemin.
Beautiful.
It's been seven minutes.
You've got your grips dialed in now.
Hey, if you're struggling, lean forward.
You guys all right there?
Adiyasuren's losing her grip a bit.
Yeah, I can tell.
It's fine. Let's just cheer them on.
Maybe suggest a diversionary tactic?
Distract yourselves!
Think of something else and breathe.
You're doing great.
You're spot on!
-The Mongolian girl's losing her grip.
-Yeah, I can see.
She's going to gas out soon.
Don't worry, guys.
Team Mongolia's pretty much done.
Don't stress it.
She's about to lose her grip.
Ten minutes.
-Bravo!
You haven't moved at all in ten minutes.
Beautiful, guys.
Team Mongolia's
struggling to even breathe.
You're amazing!
I was so tense.
I was breaking out in a cold sweat,
and my hands were as cold as ice.
I'll admit, this was nothing
like what I imagined.
Recep, I need to adjust my grip.
What's going on?
Relax and try not to move.
Our guys are losing grip on the left.
Check out those guys.
On the far side?
Drop out!
Team Türkiye's struggling.
Hold tight, guys.
Team Türkiye's struggling!
Hang in there, Enkh-Orgil.
Why was she moving around so much?
I don't know, maybe her arm fell asleep.
Don't forget this is a team challenge.
Your totems are still
as straight as a board, guys.
Can you pull in your left a bit?
Just a bit while I shift my grip.
I'm good now.
The weight's on my back now.
I'm good now, Recep. That's much better.
As time went on,
the weight of the totems
crushed my muscles more and more.
But nothing was more important
than winning the other guys,
so I continued to fight through it.
Come on, let go already.
Come on, Mongolia. Just let go.
Enkh-Orgil, pull in your left.
You're doing amazing.
-I'll pull in a bit.
-Okay.
Here you go.
We can do this. Keep holding!
Türkiye's starting to lose stability.
Recep.
Hold for a second.
Pull your left in a bit, Yasemin.
I need to relax my grip.
Okay, I got it. I got it.
Don't pull too much!
Don't pull too much,
or you'll lose balance!
My lower back started spasming hard.
Hold it.
Yasemin, Recep, keep holding!
Mongolia's fading fast.
They're going to be done soon.
It's slipping. The right hand's slipping.
You're crushing it, guys.
You're crushing it!
-You got this. Don't let go!
-Yes, Adiyasuren!
Recep, they're almost done.
Hang in there, it's not long now!
Hold it!
My elbow's killing me.
It was 135 kg on each side,
so I assumed the two of us
could easily handle it.
But as we held on,
the 135 kg totems
started feeling like 245 kg.
I'm taking on too much weight.
Recep, come on.
-Not long now.
-They've gone red in the face!
Come on, Recep.
Don't forget this is a mental game!
Hang in there!
They're done any second now!
Your left, your left.
-You're amazing, guys!
-Keep holding, Enkh-Orgil!
Stop jolting them. Keep them still.
The more you jolt them,
the harder it is to keep your grip.
They're struggling too.
Hold just a little longer.
They're struggling just as badly!
You can relax your grip again now.
Don't move around too much.
Don't jolt them!
-Yasemin, let go.
-Don't let go, Recep.
Please, Recep.
Don't do it, Recep. Please don't let go.
I'm really struggling here.
-They're done.
-Look, they're done.
Keep holding, guys. You got this.
Enkh-Orgil, stay strong!
Recep, I can't hold any longer.
Hold it, hold it!
Hold it, Recep!
-Yes!
-Yes! Türkiye's let go!
-Keep holding. You got this!
-Come on, guys!
-That's it!
Bravo.
Bravo, good effort!
I think it's his back.
He let go because of his back.
I've had two surgeries on this elbow,
and it was putting
too much strain on my arm.
-Good effort, guys.
-Don't sweat it. You did your best.
I begged and begged Recep not to let go.
But for every victory,
there must be a defeat.
That's just the way of it.
I would like to thank Yasemin.
She and I stood back-to-back
in that challenge
and gave it our best shot.
Neither of us wanted to let go, of course.
But in the end, we didn't have a choice.
I'm sad that we lost.
It's going well.
We're definitely going to hold out now
till the very end.
We need to win this
and get those three points.
-Team Türkiye's out!
-You can do this, guys!
You got this! Push through!
-Enkh-Orgil.
-Yeah?
I think we can keep going like this!
Of course we can.
Twenty minutes.
-Twenty minutes!
-Great job, guys. Keep at it!
Focus, guys.
-You got this. Balance the weight.
-Doing great, guys. Keep holding!
-Let's take turns counting to 100.
-Okay.
I'll start now, okay?
Go.
We took turns counting to 100
to distract ourselves.
One hundred. I'm done counting.
Okay.
One, two…
Looking great, you two!
You got this.
Twenty-five minutes.
-Twenty-five minutes!
-Way to go!
Nice!
You two are on fire!
I distracted myself thinking about
galloping on horseback in the hills
or across the steppe when I was a kid.
With these thoughts, I distracted myself.
Pull in your left.
Your left, your left.
Just pull in your left,
and I can keep holding my right.
Thirty-five minutes.
At around the half-hour mark,
the tendon in my right arm
started hurting.
I have a prior injury there,
and the strain made the pain unbearable.
I can't hold any longer.
Push through, guys! Keep holding.
-Pull your left again!
-Okay.
-Nice!
-That's it, guys!
Keep balancing each other out like that!
The Mongolians have tightened
their grip again.
How can they tighten it back up like that?
-That's amazing.
-It is.
-Unbelievable.
-Yeah.
Those guys were serious contenders.
We realized their record
was going to be hard to top.
I couldn't believe what I was seeing.
It was some next-level strength.
We need to watch out.
Mongolia's a real powerhouse.
What are these people eating
to have such strength?
Forty minutes.
I can't hold any longer.
Push through, Enkh-Orgil!
Enkh-Orgil, keep holding!
I got it, Enkh-Orgil!
-You can do it, you can do it.
-You got this.
You killed it, guys!
You crushed it! We've so got this!
We've won this for sure.
That was amazing.
Enkh-Orgil.
Awesome, guys.
You owned it!
-Come here, let me give you a hug.
-That was incredible.
Adiyasuren, you were amazing.
I can't believe how long you held out.
I thought that if we
kept this momentum going,
we could totally take the lead.
Physical: Asia.
We will now begin
the third game of the team rep match.
Huh? That's what we're using?
They're rings.
There are four ropes.
Why are there four?
Why are they so long?
Were we meant to hang from those things?
My head was spinning with possibilities.
We were right about the body weight.
Being light will be an advantage.
The results for the second game
were pending,
so we were
going into the third game blind.
The only thought in my head was
that we had to get those three points.
What do you think, Anıl?
Team Japan has one win so far,
and the second game is pending.
We need to gain a lead on Japan,
so we're going to go all out.
-It's calling my name.
-Right?
When it comes to pure grit,
no one beats you.
Our go-to guy for aerial stuff.
Hanging from ropes
is basically what I do for a living,
so I could probably relax
and maybe even take a nap while I'm at it.
Physical: Asia.
The third game of the team rep match,
the last one hanging match.
In the last one hanging match,
you will hang from fabric strips
suspended in the air.
You have two handholds
and two footholds to hang from.
So you use your hands and feet
simultaneously.
Thereafter, you'll be required
to change your position
according to instructions.
Gripping a single handhold with both hands
or placing both feet on a single foothold
is not allowed.
-This is all you're allowed to do then.
-Yeah.
All fours, like this?
The one representative from each country
participating in
the last one hanging match,
please enter the arena.
Go!
The third game of the team rep match.
Contestants of the last one hanging match.
Anıl Berk Baki of Team Türkiye.
ANIL BERK BAKI
NATIONAL TEAM SAILOR
Go, Anıl.
-Go, Anıl!
Anıl is a sailing athlete,
and his grip strength
puts my wrestling grip to shame.
He's the perfect guy for this job.
Nonoka Ozaki of Team Japan.
NONOKA OZAKI
NATIONAL TEAM WRESTLER
Go, Nonoka!
Go get it!
We guessed body weight
would be an important factor in this game.
And since I'm lighter than the guys,
we decided to take advantage of that
in this hanging challenge.
Lkhagva-Ochir Erdene-Ochir
of Team Mongolia.
LKHAGVA-OCHIR
CIRCUS ARTIST
Bring it!
Show them!
The third game was
who could hang in midair the longest,
so Lkhagva-Ochir
was our only possible choice.
I mean, that's his area of expertise.
It's impossible for him not to win this.
Once the whistle blows,
the match will begin.
Because of all the disruption
that went on in the second game,
we didn't get the result we wanted.
So I went into the third game
determined to leave it all out there
and clinch the win.
The only way I'm coming down from here
is if I'm dead or unconscious.
And I'm never going to give up.
First place is mine and mine only.
Find your balance. There you go.
Ready…
Nice, Nonoka. That's it.
Yeah, that's it. Fall off.
I had to hang, but I lost my balance.
I got completely freaked out.
Anıl, the other guys have locked
the ropes in with their arms. Try that.
I had to pull myself together quickly
and figure it out.
Cross your legs.
Focus, Anıl.
You've found your balance now, Anıl.
Looking good, Nonoka.
You look the most stable.
Mongolia's crossed his legs.
Take a look at him.
The Mongolian acrobat
was obviously going to be
the master at hanging from stuff,
so I decided to copy what he was doing.
See if you can copy what he's doing.
That's it, Nonoka.
Keep an eye on what Mongolia's doing.
Yeah, keep your eyes on him.
Okay, okay.
That's good.
I think they're telling them
to look at what our team is doing.
The Mongolian guy is so relaxed.
They're definitely a stacked team.
This guy was unreal.
The other two started copying me,
mirroring my every move.
It gave me more confidence
and determination to win.
Five minutes.
You're doing great, Lkhagva-Ochir!
It's only been 5 minutes?
It feels like it's been 15.
Looking great.
Türkiye's just frozen in place.
Japan's staying up pretty well
despite very little foot support.
-Come on, Nonoka.
-That's it!
The Mongolian
sure does have great balance.
-He's killing it.
-He's as still as a rock.
Your form's the best out of the three.
Check the other two whenever you can.
Ten minutes.
Great work!
Good stuff!
Come on, you got this.
It looks like one of her feet
isn't fully set in the ring.
-Yeah.
-She looks kind of unstable.
The girl isn't looking good.
Hold it.
Stay strong!
Come on, you can win this.
There you go, you're back!
Nice!
With every second,
the pain in my inner thighs got worse,
and my legs were really working it.
The one in the middle has to go.
I know. I hope she falls off.
Nineteen minutes.
In one minute,
you'll be required to release one hand.
You need to let go of one hand now,
Lkhagva-Ochir.
You need to let go of a hand soon,
so rest your other arm till then.
One hand off.
-Nice.
-Nicely done.
Take it slow.
She's not changing her position at all.
I think she's found her sweet spot.
I love that stability.
Nice, Nonoka.
You're doing great.
The Mongolian guy's
about to take a nap up there.
He totally could, you know?
That's how comfy he looks.
Good stuff, Lkhagva-Ochir.
You look so cool.
Team Mongolia was killing it.
I just couldn't believe it.
But I kept reminding myself
why we flew 11 hours to get here
and why we were pouring
so much effort into this.
I did everything I could to hold on.
You're doing great, Anıl.
That's it, Lkhagva-Ochir.
Nice.
Thirty-nine minutes.
You will shortly be required
to unlock your feet.
You'll have to unlock your feet
in one minute.
One minute from now.
Shit's getting dicey now.
It'll be even worse
if they have to spread their legs too.
Nonoka, this is when the real game starts.
You have the edge.
Being heavier makes them less stable.
Unlock.
You've got to unlock your feet.
This is it.
-Don't rush it.
-Do it slowly.
Oh no. Be careful.
Team Türkiye's in a bad spot.
The one on his left has lost balance.
Anıl, the girl on your left is losing it.
She's struggling badly.
Her face says it all.
She's tipping back and forth.
Team Türkiye's really struggling.
Come on, Türkiye. Please fall off.
Hang in there, buddy.
She's losing it. Keep it together.
Don't spread your legs!
Pull your legs in.
Subtitle translation by: Jee Butcher